Ogiji Maximilian Ondugbe

Contact

Address

Nyanya FCT Abuja, Nigeria

Phone

+2348123606666

Mail

maximilianogiji55@gmail.com

Career Profile

Good day, am Ogiji Maximilian. Am a 19year-old graduate with a Bachelor of Science from ISM Adonai where I studied Computer Science. Am a web designer, frontend developer aspiring to become a Web 3 and FullStack developer. I hail from a little village from Benue State, Nigeria called Okpoga but i reside in Abuja Nigeria. I have had some experience on my work of line (Frontend developer), I have completed some projects on Frontend Mentor, had a bootcamp on Free Code Camp, Wildlearner, JavaScript 30 and JavaScript.info. I have been able to work with tools like Git, GitHub, Trello, Vercel, CodePen, Slack. Am also good in working with people, having some projects with Simon Ogiji, Alyssa and others. 2019-2022

Technical Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript

- GitHub
- MS Office
- Google Workspace
- Excellent Communication
- Team Player

Education

Secondary School Certificate

Government Science and Technical College, Otukpa Benue State, Nigeria

September 2013- June 2019

Bachelor in Science

Institut Supérieur De Management Adonaï, Porto-Novo, Benin-Republic

September 2019- July 2022

Relevant Experience

Student

Free Code Camp

July 2022- Till Date

- I studied HTML, CSS, JavaScript and got a certificate on them.
- I studied this courses and did projects on them which awarded me my certificate.

Student

Frontend Mentor

August 2022- Till Date

- Here, I did projects on HTML, CSS and JavaScript on different levels.
- I met with other students where I helped them with their projects and vice versa.